dr. O'Connor this video is about the
anabolic steroid Anna draw can you tell
us a little bit about it
thank you very much Anna draw is
certainly one of the strongest Orlando
box steroids in the world apart from
Dyna ball it was brought into the US
market in the 1960s the early 60s and
the indication for in a draw was called
and rule 50 at that time was for medical
purpose of course all analog steroids
came into the markets mainly in America
and Europe before true medical purpose
and those purposes were always based
around muscle wasting in cachexia so
those states being associated with
people that have serious disease states
disease states that lead to cachexia and
body weight wasting it's an anabolic
steroid so it would be very good
obviously it's very good for putting on
weight and it's interesting that if you
do the research you'll see that it was
laid out for even pre operative and
post-operative care for someone that was
maybe we can debilitated and maybe even
older it was really researched for years
as a geriatric panacea which it turns
out not to because a side effects er are
so I was so strong it's it's such a
dangerous drug so for osteoporosis and
anemia so I think in the end one of the
really true medical lasting up until the
bitter end of this drug in the 1990s it
was marketed for anemia and really more
for end-stage kidney disease related
anemia so when someone has end-stage
kidney disease and that are either
heading towards dialysis or they're on
dialysis before they haven't had a
transplant they're gonna be
significantly anemic because of the the
loss of Ipoh Jen how much weight will a
user typically gain during
cycle of an our draw and that's amazing
so and Rahl is the mother of oral and
about steroids in addition to Dyna ball
and it's not uncommon for a novice user
to start using a natal 50 and to gain
upwards of 20 to 30 pounds of body
weight now most of it's a pointer but
there there a significant increase in
strength and this is a strong oral
steroid so they will gain up to 20 to 30
pounds in up to 8 weeks on and off so
tell us more about the side effects side
effects of Anna draw are very strong and
pronounced Dianna draw itself is a
derivative of DHT so it does have
properties that cause weight gain and
puffiness so puffiness and weight gain
is the most pronounced and that leads to
cardiovascular risks and hypertension
obviously it debilitates lipid panels
where HDL is go into the into the ground
significantly very dangerous and LDL bad
cholesterol will go up significantly
it's interesting this drug does not have
inherent estrogenic properties because
it's a DHT a derivative drug so it can't
aromatize but it does have its own
property of stimulating the estrogen
receptor itself and there's some thought
of other mediums and prolactin based
stimulation that leads to a surge etic
effects and that's the the bloatedness
and the water weight gain with the side
effects hair loss you know real
antigenic steroid related issues going
on hair loss acne can be significantly
bad very very bad and you will see the
anabolic steroid induced hypogonadism
the central nervous system
how does Ana draw compared I animal so
these are the two big brothers you know
there's D ball and Ana draw a bombs and
draw 50 otherwise known a bombs back in
the day still today on the black market
office
so the they're very similar they're just
very similar actually and they're there
they're used interchangeably I don't
know that many many guys to use and roll
and D ball together they'll use either
and draw or D ball in that part of the
bulking cycle and that based on the
genetics and based on what they're doing
and look for and other drugs that
they're on and what their their scope is
and what they're trying to perform its
enhance either muscle building or a
strength or activity they'll pick this
drug or dinoball but in the end this is
a stronger drug very very strong toxic
drug what doses do bodybuilders
typically use so angela fifty obviously
is fifty milligrams of this medicine you
know this in a box steroid called ana
draw interesting historically it was
first on the market back in the 60s and
they had doses two point five milligrams
two point five five and ten milligram
tablets and there are different
suppliers in different manufacturers but
in the end it's the big integer all
fifty that is used so that's one tablet
and it will typically be used one tablet
a day steroid user will use one or two a
day and typically usually not more than
three tablets a day so three a bombs
three an adult tablets a day is a
massive cycle and again with or without
testosterone decade rob one or all the
other anabolic steroids are classically
missed the inner muscular steroids so i
have seen as an expert in anabolic
steroids obviously myself i've seen man
use up to ten in all tablets a day ten a
bombs a day and with with that kind of
use prolonged massive medical problems
in side effects what's the legal status
legal status like any other anabolic
steroid in america for what it is is
completely illicit and illegal does
nothing more to say it's an illegal drug
thank you again doctor oh god i hope
this helps and thank you very much thank
you